{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610516328","data":{"timestamp":" 947610516328"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610517372","data":{"timestamp":" 947610517372"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610520703","data":{"timestamp":" 947610520703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610521751","data":{"timestamp":" 947610521751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610525135","data":{"timestamp":" 947610525135"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610526173","data":{"timestamp":" 947610526172"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610529065","data":{"timestamp":" 947610529065"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610530714","data":{"timestamp":" 947610530714"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610533175","data":{"timestamp":" 947610533175"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610533293","data":{"timestamp":" 947610533293"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610534237","data":{"timestamp":" 947610534236"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610537125","data":{"timestamp":" 947610537125"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610543793","data":{"timestamp":" 947610543793"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610544863","data":{"timestamp":" 947610544863"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610550213","data":{"timestamp":" 947610550213"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610551303","data":{"timestamp":" 947610551302"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610555489","data":{"timestamp":" 947610555488"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610556553","data":{"timestamp":" 947610556552"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610560518","data":{"timestamp":" 947610560517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610561588","data":{"timestamp":" 947610561588"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610564943","data":{"timestamp":" 947610564942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610565999","data":{"timestamp":" 947610565998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610572505","data":{"timestamp":" 947610572504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610573568","data":{"timestamp":" 947610573567"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610577345","data":{"timestamp":" 947610577345"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610578403","data":{"timestamp":" 947610578402"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610584773","data":{"timestamp":" 947610584773"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610585837","data":{"timestamp":" 947610585837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610588536","data":{"timestamp":" 947610588536"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610589579","data":{"timestamp":" 947610589579"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610592184","data":{"timestamp":" 947610592184"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610593246","data":{"timestamp":" 947610593245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610598280","data":{"timestamp":" 947610598279"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610599340","data":{"timestamp":" 947610599340"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610602772","data":{"timestamp":" 947610602772"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610603819","data":{"timestamp":" 947610603818"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610606585","data":{"timestamp":" 947610606585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610607642","data":{"timestamp":" 947610607641"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610610282","data":{"timestamp":" 947610610282"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610611331","data":{"timestamp":" 947610611330"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610613915","data":{"timestamp":" 947610613914"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610614975","data":{"timestamp":" 947610614974"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610628465","data":{"timestamp":" 947610628464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610629532","data":{"timestamp":" 947610629531"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610652434","data":{"timestamp":" 947610652434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610653522","data":{"timestamp":" 947610653522"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610660201","data":{"timestamp":" 947610660200"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610661276","data":{"timestamp":" 947610661275"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610664704","data":{"timestamp":" 947610664703"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610664789","data":{"timestamp":" 947610664789"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" 1fec3e29-3d2d-4a42-acae-2732a7136ae9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610738619","data":{"timestamp":" 947610738619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610802377","data":{"timestamp":" 947610802377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610804683","data":{"timestamp":" 947610804683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610864797","data":{"timestamp":" 947610864797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610867384","data":{"timestamp":" 947610867384"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610898810","data":{"timestamp":" 947610898810"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610901414","data":{"timestamp":" 947610901413"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_64","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610933102","data":{"timestamp":" 947610933102"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947610933169","data":{"timestamp":" 947610933169"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000111_200819"," gameId":" cde68ebb-698c-4cb7-8779-e405856cecca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_64"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi zote tofauti zilimkumbusha Bweha kila mara kutokuwa mjinga tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}